OLUWABUSAYO VICTORIA **AROWOSAFE**

(506)-998-1841 | Fredericton, New Brunswick E3B 2A7 oluwabusayo.arowosafe@gmail.com

LANGUAGE CAPABILITY: ENGLISH

Enthusiastic and self-motivated Master of Business Administration graduate with five years experience in administration and office management. eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail, problem solving and excellent communication skills. Clear understanding of Microsoft Office Suite with experience in working with confidential information and administrative processes and practices.

EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2022 - TILL DATE

MEDICAL OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR - DR E. ANOCHIE CLINIC

- Perform administrative and clerical duties such as sending faxes, emails, receiving phone enquiries, tracking budgets and reconciling financial records.
- Manage and perform a variety of office duties including patient referral, registration and appointment scheduling.
- Scan new information such as daily progress notes, physical exams, labs and diagnostic testing into EMR.
- Process confidential patient information and requests while ensuring compliance with HIPAA privacy and security regulations.
- Manage the information and data management system to ensure the accuracy of patients' details, medical history, reports, requisitions and treatment plans.

JANUARY 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

TECHNICAL AND ADMINISTRATIVE SUPPORT - SAINT JOSEPH HERITAGE HOSPITALS

- Develop and implement performance improvement strategies and plans to promote continuous improvement during covid testing.
- Collaborate with management to modify weekly or daily schedules to accommodate the needs of the organization.
- Ensure patient medical records are private and secure during covid testing.
- Ensure all departments comply with the current healthcare laws and regulations.
- Exhibits polite and professional communication via phone, e-mail, and mail.
- Monitor the department's budget and prepare accurate reports about your findings.

SEPTEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

HOME HEALTHCARE ADMINISTRATOR - 24HR HOMECARE, FULLERTON, CALIFORNIA

- Perform confidentiality obligations by keeping client information and client list private.
- Lead branch location growth and organizational goals as well as day to day activities.
- Provide oversight of the needs of patients referred to home care services.

- Provide information about health system education and standards, patient rights and health information privacy.
- Ensure records of employee files are maintained accurately.
- Ensure that the numbers and qualifications of personnel available to provide and supervise services are sufficient to implement the plans of care and treatment to meet the medical and nursing needs of the clients.
- Ensure that provided health services are specifically tailored to meet customer's needs.

AUGUST 2014 - NOVEMBER 2017

LABORATORY ADMINISTRATOR - GENESIS MEDICAL DIAGNOSTIC LABORATORY, IBADAN, NIGERIA

- Perform administrative and clerical duties such as sending faxes, emails, receiving phone enquiries, tracking budgets and reconciling financial records.
- Responsible for the overall operation and administration of the laboratory.
- Establish and maintain quality control and quality assurance programs to assure the quality of laboratory services provided and to identify failures in quality as they occur.
- Ensure that the test methodologies selected have the capability of providing the quality of results required for patient care
- Participate in the development and implementation of operations budget to ensure compliance with organizational expenditure requirements.
- Ensure operational adherence to accepted technical service standards for laboratory medicine.

EDUCATION

DECEMBER 2019

MASTER OF BUSINESS
ADMINISTRATION
WESTCLIFF UNIVERSITY - IRVINE,
CALIFONIA.
GRADUATED WITH AN AVERAGE G.P.A OF
3.73

APRIL 2014
B.SC MICROBIOLOGY,
UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN - OYO STATE,
NIGERIA

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Organization and time management
- Interpersonal Communication
- Multitasking abilities

- Problem solving
- Detail-oriented
- Analytical skills
- Proficient in Microsoft Office